I'm watching you from over here!
You better not stop!
Rocket Engine Valve.
Hello.
I am Rocket Engine Valve.
Huh? Momo?
Jiji?
Yo. You're finally here.
I heard all about it from your mom.
Huh? What? Why is he here?
Who is that?
That guy is Momo's childhood friend...
and her first love.
Miss Ayase's first crush?
He looks so cool.
From how he's dressed,
he's definitely an athlete.
He looks really sincere, too.
Miss Ayase falling for him
must mean that he's a proper guy.
Momo, you're such a cutie!
And your terrible impression...
So priceless!
It's been a while, Momo.
Wanna hug for starters?
So annoying. What's with you?
I got me an "annoying"!
Gimme more!
Okarun, help me kill this guy.
Long time no see, Jiji.
Oh, good evening!
It's been a while!
You're still as beautiful as ever, Auntie!
You've grown up into quite the genius.
Well, come on in.
Huh? Wait a sec, what's going on here?
What? Isn't it obvious?
He's gonna live with us starting today.
Huh? What for?
Absolutely not!
"Absolutely!" and "Not!"
still means you like it!
Are you a genius?
Thanks for having me, fam!
Whoa! What about my permission!?
L-Live together?
It's too unnatural.
Is she getting another new demon?
Can it be that she's diligently
gathering allies
to prepare for the coming of Ragnarok,
the final war?
I don't think that's it.
I won't allow it, Momo Ayase!
What's up with you?
I can totally see through your schemes!
We're temporary allies
against the alien threat,
but once that's over, you're next!
Huh? Is she still hooked on that idea?
Seems so.
I will gather forces as well
to challenge your Ragnarok!
See you!
Thanks for your effort.
All these troublesome things
came rushing over at once!
Well, I'll head home now, too.
Oh. Okay.
Take care.
Okay.
Hey, Okarun.
Huh?
What is it?
"See you tomorrow!"
It's your turn to say it, Okarun!
Huh?
We're taking turns?
We are! So just say it!
Oh, er...
Um...
See you...
tomorrow.
Good.
Okay.
I'm not convinced.
KEEP OUT
JIJI'S ROOM
Why is Jiji living at our place?
Give me a proper explanation.
Auntie's cooking is too good!
Are you a genius?
Are you listening?
I told you already.
Both of Jiji's parents
have been hospitalized.
But why our place?
You usually go to a relative's house
in times like this.
You're so cold-hearted.
Society is about helping each other out.
Auntie, you're so cool.
Come on now, Jiji.
You really are a genius.
Make sure to eat up!
Tank you!
He just got you by the heartstrings!
Don't be dumb. Nobody's ever gotten me
by my heartstrings.
Auntie, you're a serious cutie!
Jiji, just how much of a genius are you?
Make sure to eat up, okay?
Tank you!
There's definitely something funny going on.
I meant something is weird!
Did we get along that well to begin with?
Back in grade school,
I made fun of you, Momo.
Looking back now, I seriously regret it.
Thing is...
I can see ghosts now.
Wait, did you pick up
a golden ball by any chance?
Golden ball?
Did I make a dirty joke at some point?
Oh, no. Forget I said that.
I moved away, so we went
to different middle schools, right?
We moved way out into the mountains.
I've always liked places with lots of nature.
And the new house was big and clean,
so I was all hyped up in the beginning.
But gradually, I started feeling
like something was off.
It's hard to explain, but the things
lying around, the toilet, the bathroom...
They were somehow different
than usual.
I told my parents,
but they wouldn't listen.
I had to convince myself
that I was imagining things.
I lived each day pretending
I didn't notice anything.
But it became so clear
and was telling me to look at it.
It went out of its way
to show itself before me.
And ever since, I see it all the time.
My parents' health started
going downhill from there.
That's why I asked famous
spirit mediums for an exorcism.
And when I did,
three of the five committed suicide.
JUNE
SUNHEIGHTS
PHOTO FOR RECORDS
DECEMBER
VALLEY OF SNAKES
PHOTO FOR RECORDS
APRIL
NORTHERN MOUNTAIN TRACKS
PHOTO FOR RECORDS
Veteran spirit mediums couldn't exorcise it.
And the person they recommended me
as my last hope...
was Momo's Auntie.
So that's what's going on.
You should've just told me sooner!
That old hag didn't even mention
you were coming.
But it was probably the right thing
to do to come to us.
Momo.
I'm sorry.
Wait, can you stop that?
Sorry for what?
All sorts of stuff.
Like how I made fun of you in the past.
How I'm roping you
into something this dangerous.
If you're gonna apologize,
don't come asking for help.
It's fine. My grandma's really tough.
I'm sure she'll beat
that evil spirit with one blow.
I ain't gonna do nothing.
Huh?
Like I said, I can only use my powers
within Kamigoe City.
Momo will take on this request.
Say what? You didn't tell me this!
Hold up!
Did you just call Auntie "Grandma"?
Someone who couldn't see ghosts
can see them now.
Maybe that golden ball
has something to do with it.
If you take this request, I'll buy you
as many uniforms as you want.
So go blow down that cursed house.
Hey there! I transferred schools!
EPISODE 11
FIRST LOVE
Bo-Bo-Bo-Boom!
I'm Jin Enjoji.
Please call me Jiji!
Whoa, he's cool!
He's a hottie!
Enjoji's parents...
You're such a cutie!
...uh, are both in the hospital now.
Oh, this is terrible. If I don't get
your contact info, it'll kill me!
I'm sure he's having a hard time,
so everyone, please help him out.
He'll be sitting next to Ayase.
You guys are relatives, right?
Nope! We're family!
We're neither of those.
Flashy guys are annoying.
Stabbed! Thank you for that
tasty roast from a beauty!
Beauty?
Momo, this guy's all good.
He's a hottie.
Hey! I'm a super hottie!
Pout, pout!
Wait, I'm being drawn ever closer.
It's because you're too cute.
What's with him? He's hilarious!
Oui!
Yeah, so who is he?
How to put it...
A childhood friend-type
from grade school.
We're living together!
What? For real?
Hey, stop that!
You'll start strange rumors!
Let me explain everything
properly in order.
- Wait, Momo...
- No, it's not...
Lovey...
dovey!
Momo and I are in
a parentally approved relationship!
Living together?
Seriously?
You can't do that!
Momo already has Okarun!
"Jealous" is an "adjective"
which describes nouns.
For instance, you can
"be jealous of another's happiness."
It's bugging me.
Miss Ayase's first crush...
Does she still like him?
He called Miss Ayase "Momo,"
and said she was cute.
Could their feelings be mutual?
So "beautiful" and "cool"
are adjectives as well.
If Miss Ayase were to start dating him...
will she stop being so kind to me?
I'm sure she'll be interested in
his hobbies and lose interest in the occult.
I won't be able to talk about
the occult during recess anymore.
Maybe I won't be able to hang out
with Miss Ayase anymore.
I'm no good.
Stop distracting yourself, Ken!
Physical training is more important
right now than such thoughts!
Oh, there you are.
What're you doing?
Practicing a new ultimate move?
Miss Ayase, you already ate lunch?
I'm gonna eat here.
Huh?
I'm watching over you
so you don't do anything funny again.
Watching over me?
That incident with Miss Shiratori
wasn't my fault.
Okarun, did you eat lunch?
Not yet.
If both your hands are tied up...
I'll feed you.
Huh?
I-Is that all right?
Momo!
Oh? You're the guy
who was at Momo's place yesterday.
You a friend?
What do you want? Weren't you gonna eat
with Miko and the others?
Oh? Is Momo-chan jealous?
Such a cutie!
As if.
Check it out!
Yogurt-flavored Pompy!
Are you serious?
Present for you, woo!
This is futile.
I can't watch Miss Ayase amicably
talk to that guy any longer.
I'll try not to see her anymore.
That will be the best move for myself,
and for Miss Ayase.
I'm not gonna give up!
Oh.
Miss Ayase!
I'm scared!
Get outta my way!
Nobody can stop me!
Huh? What is it this time?
Whoa, what's that?
Seriously wicked!
Stop right there, you half-wit!
Momo, let's run for it!
Don't get in my way!
Momo!
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Okarun! His ball...
It's golden!
Momo, hide behind me!
- Jiji, calm down!
- Hold it!
You're not getting away!
You've got some nerves!
Okarun!
Miss Ayase!
- Stop this guy!
- Momo! Hang onto me!
Wait, you right there!
Get away from Miss Ayase!
I don't like it.
I want him to get away from her.
Damn you! I know you're trying
to stop me, but I won't stop!
You make me limp.
Another monster came out!
Okarun!
- Okarun!
- Momo-chan! The power lines!
Momo-chan! Where is he?
There!
Thanks, Okarun! You're a lifesaver!
A monster captured us!
I'll protect you, Momo!
Stop that! Okarun is on our side!
He was with us earlier!
No way! For real?
Here goes!
All right, Okarun, brace yourself!
Jiji, help us out!
Give up already, you piece of crap!
We'll slowly pull him here!
No way! I'm not gonna give up!
I don't wanna give up!
Ew! Gross!
Merge!
Momo, he's getting away!
Okarun, after him!
No good. We lost sight of him.
S-So amazing.
He transformed and stuff.
What should we do? We don't even
know which way he went.
This way!
Huh? What was that?
Miss Ayase, what have you been doing?
KEEP OUT
Here?
Is it all right to barge in without asking?
Oh.
Goddamn it.
I was so close.
Miss Ayase, how did you know
where he was headed to?
He looks like he's exhausted?
When he split apart to escape,
I managed to grab just his heart.
I punched it on a hunch, and that
was when I heard him screaming in agony.
Freaky!
Woo! Not bad!
I feel a little sorry for him.
It's not like we want to catch and eat you.
If you'll promise not to run away,
I'll give you your heart back.
So can you show us your golden nuts?
It might be one of my friend's.
Miss Ayase, can you
please say it more delicately?
Are dirty jokes that popular nowadays?
Taro? Is that you, Taro?
Hana!
Where are you, Hana?
No! Don't come here!
Please go back, Taro!
No way! I will never give up!
I won't give up on you, Hana!
What? What's going on here?
I found you!
I finally found you!
Why did you come here?
Why did you put yourself
through so much danger?
Because I love you!
Everything changed after I met you.
My world used to be grey,
but thanks to you,
it became so colorful!
We can't!
Our manufacturer's dates
are too far apart!
We live in different worlds!
My duties are all over!
Please hurry back.
Otherwise you'll turn into
oversized trash, too!
I don't care.
You're the one I fell in love with.
I won't let go of you no matter what!
Let's run away together!
If I don't do anything right here and now,
I'll regret it for the rest of my life!
Taro!
UMAs were all said to be nonsense,
but they are "Unidentified Mysterious Animals"
so they are simply "unidentified" biologically!
What's suddenly gotten into you?
Woo! You're so passionate, Okarun!
Next episode,
"Let's Go to the Cursed House"!
EPISODE 12
LET'S GO TO THE CURSED HOUSE
- So, what got into you now?
- In other words, I'll never give up!